# Patrick Huynh

A hard-working and community-oriented student with over 5 years of experience in IT support. Well versed in various fields of technical support such as software and hardware. Currently holds an active <a href="CompTIA A+ Certification">CompTIA A+ Certification</a>.

## **EXPERIENCE**

## **AgeCare Limited** — Service Desk Analyst

**JANUARY 2023 - PRESENT** 

- Provided first level technical support, investigation, and diagnosis of incidents remotely.
- Supported users in the use of computer equipment by providing necessary training and advice.
- Worked on projects such as an on-premise to Microsoft 365 migration of Exchange mailboxes.
- Utilised SDP OnDemand, Okta, Box, and Microsoft Entra to resolve tickets.

# **Pacific National Exhibition** — Ticket Office Attendant

**AUGUST 2022 - PRESENT** 

- Handled various payment methods, completing seller reports at the end of the day.
- Scanned tickets and helped customers navigate through the park.

# **Long View Systems** — IT Support Technician

**AUGUST 2022** 

- Reimaged, deployed, and secured laptops (installation of M365, antivirus, domain server, etc...)
- Configured iPads and mobile devices to the BlackBerry Unified Endpoint Manager allowing for remote management.
- Troubleshooted and solved login, network, email, and printing issues with end users then educated them for the future.
- Adhered to WCB regulations and WHMIS guidelines onsite.

#### **EDUCATION**

# **David Thompson Secondary**, Vancouver — High School

SEPTEMBER 2019 - PRESENT

- Over **400** hours of service contributed to the school
- Enrolled in the <u>DT Odyssey Advanced Placement Program</u>
- Secretary of the DT Maker Club
- Tech Specialist of Student Council Executive Team
- Tech Specialist of the David Thompson Science Club
- Tech Specialist of the <u>David Thompson Counselling Department</u>
- Executive Member of the David Thompson Code Club

**+1** (604) 619-9828

patrick@patrickh.ca

natrickh.ca

in linkedin.com/in/patricklbh

#### INTERPERSONAL SKILLS

Multitasking

**Problem Solving** 

Critical Thinking

Adaptability

Communication

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

HTML / CSS / JS - 4 years

Python - 3 years

Technical Support - 6 years

#### **AWARDS**

### 2022 SHAD Design Challenge Winner

Developed a portable safety device that alerts the user of threats in the environment.

# 2022 UBC Engineering Design Competition Winner

Developed & engineered a solution to food shortages with a group.

#### 2021 GVRSF Silver Award

Awarded silver at the Greater Vancouver Regional Science Fair.

#### **LANGUAGES**

- English Fluent
- Cantonese Fluent
- French Limited
- Mandarin Limited